Guide to the Howard Scott Labor Ephemera Collection, 1894-2004 AIS.1999.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Badges and Pins, III.
  - "Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers 585: Washington, Pennsylvania", October 1961; 57.
  - "United We Bargain, Divided We Beg! Anne Feeney and Friends", 58.
  - "St. Mary's Church N.S. Pittsburgh, PA Diamond Jubilee", 1923; 59.
  - "Labor Day Altoona, PA", 1920; 60.
  - "Annual Convention, German-American Federation of Penna.: Pittsburgh, PA", June 20-21, 1931; 61.
  - "UE-CIO: We Need A Wage Increase Now!", 62.
  - "Wage Raise Now: Protect UE Wages, Support Beaver Strikers", 63.
  - "UE Local 1150", October-December 1955; 64.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. Industrial Union 1138 CIO", August 1938; 65.
  - "My Union! My Party! UE Shop Club for the Labor Party", 66-67.
  - "Unite: UE Public Employees for the Labor Party", 68.
  - "Allegheny-Kiski Valley Trades Council 908", October-December 1970; 69.
  - "Unidade, Unidad, Unity: UE Plastic Workers Organizing Committee", 70.
  - "Bakery Drivers Union Local 485", April 1937; 71.
  - "A Good Time With the Butchers", June 23, 1909; 72.
  - "Picnic & Union Meeting: B. of L.F.&E., L.S.B. of L.F.&E. Erie, PA" Brotherhood of Local Firemen and Engineers and Ladies Society, August 16-17, 1929; 73.
  - "Windber Local No. 6186/Scalp Level Local No. 5229 U.M.W. of America: Labor Day Picnic, Recreation Park, Windber, PA", 74.
  - "Retail Food Store Employees Union: A.M.C.&B.W. of N.A. 590, A.F. of L.", 1945; 75.
  - "Steel City Lodge 591 A.F. of L., B. of R.C.", 1940; 76.
  - "Vote Yes!! United We Bargain: SEIU COGS Local 150 AFL-CIO", 77-79.
  - "United We Bargain Divided We Beg: SEIU COGS Local 150 AFL-CIO", 80.
  - "Engineer's Union Local 66 Pittsburgh, PA", June 1942; 81.
  - "Labor's Non-Partisan League: Elect Endorsed Candidates", 82.
  - "1st Annual Celebration, United Labor Council Tarentum, PA", May 12, 1934; 83.
  - "Pittsburgh Association for the Improvement of the Poor 47", 84.
  - "Carpenter's for Kerry", 2004; 85.
  - "I Am A Pensioned Coal Miner Thanks To John L. Lewis", 86.
  - "Laborers Local 1058 Steward", 87.
  - "Save Dorothy 6", 88.